Hi friends, I am Sanket Chaudhary and you are
watching friends, today we are going to talk about ICICI Prudential
shares. However, who has
predicted a rise to 14, we will
tell you when we see the
result of this. After the BSE results, the brokerage may become bullish
on 14. So, if we look at it, then
see, the
net profit of ICICI Prudential for January-March had increased by 19 percent annually.
Now see, the profit of the company during this period was
Rs 519 crore.
In the previous financial year, now
look at the profit of this company which was Rs 436 crore,
Sher Khan has
estimated that there may be a rally on 14. So let's see, the
insurance company ICICI Prudential shares, which are brokerage firms, are
looking bullish, so Sher Khan has
expressed hope of a rise in it.
However, the company has announced the results of the March quarter.
Today, on April 18, the shares of ICICI Prudential were at
3.45 percent, which has shown a rise in it.
This stock closed at Rs 06 today,
so look at how rapidly the company's market has
increased to
Rs 84.52 crore. The stock's
92-week high today is Rs
17.40, while its weekly low was
shown at Rs 1056. So see what is the target
price, you can see in this, the brokerage
firm Sher Khan has
given a buy rating to IC shares in its research report on April 18, 2024. The
brokerage has set a target price of Rs 1950 for it. According to this, a
rally of 14 percent can be expected for the company's shares. The
brokerage believes that the company has a
healthy premium market share with
profitable growth.
After using data analysis, they had done
a focused strategy of balanced growth and risk selection,
which
they told us that we expect
high mintage
and premium growth due to investment in distribution channels and leveraging digital capabilities. So they have given growth.  The
combined ratio is estimated to be 14:14. He further said that the combined ratio should
gradually improve and profitability should
increase. We are optimistic about the company's planned
growth plan
and we hope that the company will give a RE of
18 to 20 in the medium term. At the
current price, the stock will be at
x 33.2 x. So, as per the report of the third result of ICC,
its profit has
increased by 19 percent on an annual basis and during this period the
company's profit was Rs 519 crore.
In the last ten years, the
company had a profit of Rs 400.3 crore in the same period. The
net premium of the company has
increased by 4000.47 in one year.
As I can tell you, there has been a huge increase of
18 percent in it, so now it has become
4767, i.e. Rs 4700 crore. So, the
ratios of the company have also
seen improvement.
Compared to 2.51, it has come down to 2.62. The dividend announced by ICICI Ltd
for its shareholders was
also an excellent one. The company has
recommended a final dividend of Rs. per share, which means you will also get a dividend,
like on
April 17, on the
occasion of Ram Navami, the markets were closed, so let's see, the
markets were closed yesterday due to this, like
due to Ram Navami, so that's all in this video, so
you should also pay a little attention, there may be a
slight rise in it, so pay a
little attention in this, a rise of 14
means a lot, so okay, thank you.